gamovideo.com 2018-08-13

# GamoVideo

### Privacy Policy

Your privacy is important to us. We have prepared this Privacy Policy to explain how we collect, use, protect, and disclose Personal Information and Usage Data when you use the GamoVideo online file hosting service ("Service"). This Privacy Policy also explains your choices for managing your information and your preferences. 

This Privacy Policy may be revised from time to time. By using the Service, you agree to be bound and to abide by the most recent version of this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy was last updated on: February 16, 2018. 

Personal Data Collection and Use 

Data You Choose to Provide to Us 

GamoVideo collects Personal Data during your registration at our Digital Purposes, when you choose to provide it, such as your name and email address. 

The decision to provide such data is optional. However, if you choose not to register or provide this data, you may not be able to access certain features or services, available within our Digital Properties. 

Your consent to the collection and use of Personal Data will be logged by us. 

In addition, you can voluntarily provide us with additional data in forms as part of the registration process. The voluntary provision of this data is a consent to the use of the data. 

GamoVideo may use the Personal Data you choose to provide to us to operate and improve our Digital Purposes, such as to provide notices about our Website, Services and Apps, process your Service inquiries, and request customer feedback. 

GamoVideo may also use such Personal Data to send you the information regarding new Products, Services or features available within our Digital Properties; solely in accordance with your granted permissions. 

You may unsubscribe from our newsletters and marketing emails anytime. 

For further info about your consent withdrawal and other opt-out options, please refer to "Your Choice and Control" section of this Privacy Policy, below. 

Personal Data Obtained from the Use of our Digital Properties 

We may also collect additional data through our Digital Properties that may include (a combination of) Personal Data elements, such as: 

Location information & IP address 

Such Personal data is collected and stored in the pseudonymized manner and can not be attributed separately to identify or reveal a natural person's individual identity. 

The collected Personal Data may be used for such purposes as: 

To respond to your inquiries and requests. 

To operate our Digital Properties and improve your experience. 

To conduct research about Digital Properties usage. 

For advertising purposes in order to deliver the most relevant ads to you. 

Managing Your Information Preferences 

You can review, correct, update, or change your Personal Information, or opt out of any direct marketing in which we may engage, by changing the relevant setting in your GamoVideo profile or account (if you have one), or by e-mailing us at support (at) gamovideo.info. If you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, please e-mail us at support (at) gamovideo.info. 

Information We Collect and How We Collect It 

Personal Information. You can use certain features of the Service without providing us with any information that identifies or may be used to directly identify you ("Personal Information"). We collect certain Personal Information when you register with GamoVideo, including your username and e-mail address. 

Usage Data. We automatically collect usage information that does not directly identify an individual user ("Usage Data"). For example, each time you use the Service we may automatically collect the type of Web browser you use, your operating system, your IP address, the links you use, and the time and duration of your use of the Service. We use this Usage Data to help us understand how people use the Service, and to enhance the services we offer. None of this information can be used to directly identify you, and we will not use it for the purpose of attempting to identify you. Please be aware, however, that we may be required to disclose information such as your IP address (a unique numerical identifier for your computer that may or may not change over time) which could be used by others to attempt to identify you. 

Cookies and Web Beacons. We use cookies (a small text file placed on your computer to identify your computer and Web browser when you use the Service). We may also use Web beacons (an electronic file placed on a website that monitors usage). We do not use cookies or Web beacons to collect Personal Information. We use cookies and Web beacons to improve the quality of the Service. Most Web browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can reset your Web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, certain features of the Service may not work if you delete or disable cookies. Some of our Service Providers, as discussed below, may use their own cookies or Web beacons in connection with the services they perform on our behalf. 

How We Use Information and When We May Share Information 

Generally. We generally use Personal Information only for purposes of providing and communicating with you about the Service, including responding to your requests, notifying you of new products or services, and otherwise communicating with you about the Service. We will not disclose Personal Information to third parties without your consent, except as explained in this Privacy Policy. 

Ad Networks. We may work with third-party advertising and marketing companies ("Ad Networks"). These companies may collect and use information about your use of the Service in order to provide advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you. Advertisements may be shown via the Services, or third-party websites. These companies may place or recognize a unique cookie on your computer or use other technologies such as Web beacons to collect information about your use of the Service and of other Internet services and websites. Our Privacy Policy does not cover any collection or use of information about you by any Ad Network. It also does not cover any information that you may choose to provide to an Ad Network or to an advertiser whose goods or services are advertised through the Service. For more information about collection and use of information by Ad Networks, and to opt-out of certain advertising, please visit http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp. 

Standard Analytics Information. We may use, and disclose to third parties, certain Usage Data regarding the Service. However, such information does not identify you individually. 

Data Retention. We will hold your Personal Information on our systems for as long as is necessary for the relevant activity. If you cancel your registration and your account is deleted GamoVideo will no longer use the Personal Information, but for administration purposes it will stay on our system for a period of one year before being deleted. 

Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement. GamoVideo cooperates with government and law enforcement officials and private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We may disclose Personal Information and any other information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties if, in our discretion, we believe it is necessary or appropriate for any of the following reasons: to respond to legal requests (including court orders and subpoenas); to protect the safety, property, or rights of GamoVideo, any GamoVideo user, or any third party; to prevent or stop any illegal, unethical, or legally actionable activity; or to comply with the law. 

Your Choice and Control 

We do our best to provide you choice and control, with regard to Personal Data and other information you provide to us. 

It is not necessary for you to provide us with any Personal Data in order to visit our Website and use our Services, although certain information is be collected automatically during your visit (as described above). 

If you register a GamoVideo account, you can control your Personal Data in a number of ways within your your GamoVideo account settings on our Website: Right to Withdraw Consent 

You may withdraw your consent to the collection and use of Personal Data by GamoVideo - generally or with regard to the additionally voluntarily communicated data in accordance with effect for the future. 

However, in the event of your cancellation, certain features that require registration may no longer be provided. This does not apply to the revocation to collect further voluntary data, provided to us. 

To withdraw your consent to the collection and use of your Personal Data by GamoVideo, please send us a corresponding inquiry via email support (at) gamovideo.info. 

Sharing Personal Data with Other Users 

GamoVideo enables you to store or share Your Content, access or download content, shared by other users. GamoVideo doesn't claim ownership of Your Content. 

When you share Your Content with others, you acknowledge that they may be able to save, record, reproduce, share, transmit, broadcast, display or otherwise use Your Content without providing any compensation to you. 

If any of your Content contains (a combination of) Personal Data elements or any other information that you would not like to share, you can limit other users' access to this Content within your GamoVideo account by making a file "Private" or setting up "Private access" to a folder, correspondingly. 

GamoVideo doesn't use what you say in email, chat, your files, documents, photos, videos and other Content to target advertising to you. 

Security 

GamoVideo is very concerned about safeguarding the confidentiality of your Personal Information. We employ reasonable physical and electronic measures designed to protect your information from unauthorized access. However, no data transmission over the Internet or other network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect information transmitted on or through the Service, we cannot and do not guarantee the of any information you upload, store, share, transmit, or provide on or through the Service, and you do so at your own risk. 

Data Retention 

GamoVideo will not retain, use or process shared Personal Data, such as your email address, for longer than necessary to fulfill our business purpose. 

We store non-personally intrusive data and the Personal Data obtained from the Use of our Digital Properties, in a pseudonymized manner, up to one year in order to ensure that our Digital Properties function properly. 

Data Integrity, Purpose of Limitation 

We process information in a way that is compatible with and relevant to the purpose for which it was collected as described above. To the extent necessary for those purposes, we take reasonable steps to ensure that any information in our care is accurate, complete, current and reliable for its intended use. 

Links To Content and to Other Websites 

Our Service permits users to share links to materials stored on servers owned by or operated on behalf of GamoVideo. Our Service may also contain links to other websites, or allow others to send you such links. The use of the Service to provide a link to material on GamoVideo servers or to a third party's website does not mean that we endorse it or that we are affiliated with it. We do not exercise control over the content uploaded and shared using the Service (except that we may remove or disable access to it upon receipt of proper notice under our Intellectual Property and Rights Policy). We also do not exercise control over third-party websites. You access such content or third-party websites at your own risk. You should always read the privacy policy of a third-party website before providing any information to the operator of the website. 

Children's Privacy 

We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under the age of 16. By using our Services, you promise that you are at least 16 years old. If we become aware that a user is under the age of 16, we will terminate any account that user may have with GamoVideo. If we become aware that we have inadvertently received Personal Information from a child under the age of 16, we will delete such information from our records.
